Register of the T. V. (Tzu-wen) Soong papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Office File, 1942-1949
  - Telegrams
    - China Defense Supplies, 1942
      Box/Folder 10: 15
    - Incoming, 1942 October 22 - 1943 March 1
      Box/Folder 11: 1
    - Outgoing, 1942 October 23 - 1943 March 5
      Box/Folder 11: 2-3
    - Duplicates, 1942 October 23 - 1943 February 5 (Reel 11)
      Box/Folder 11: 4-5
    - Incoming, 1942 November 17-December 30
      Box/Folder 11: 6-7
    - Outgoing, 1942 November 19-December 30
      Box/Folder 11: 8
    - Miscellany, 1942 October 22 - 1943 August 24
      Box/Folder 11: 9
    - China Defense Supplies, 1942 October - 1943 February
      Box/Folder 12: 1-2
    - Chungking, incoming, 1942 October 5 - 1943 January 2 (Reel 12)
      Box/Folder 12: 3-5
    - Chungking, outgoing, 1942 October 6 - 1943 January 4
      Box/Folder 12: 6-8
    - Outgoing, 1942 January 5 - 1943 October 6
      Box/Folder 12: 9-11
    - Calcutta, 1943 (Reel 13)
      Box/Folder 13: 1
    - China Defense Supplies, 1943
      Box/Folder 13: 2-5
    - Chungking, 1943 January-March
      Box/Folder 13: 6
    - Chungking, 1943 January-March (Reel 14)
      Box/Folder 13: 7-8
    - Moscow, 1943
      Box/Folder 13: 9
    - New Delhi, 1943
      Box/Folder 13: 10
    - Vically, 1943
      Box/Folder 13: 11
    - Washington, 1943
      Box/Folder 13: 12
    - Incoming, 1943
      Box/Folder 13: 13-14
    - Outgoing, 1943
      Box/Folder 13: 15-16
    - Incoming, 1943 January 5-October 2
      Box/Folder 14: 1-2
    - Incoming, 1943 January 5-October 2 (Reel 15)
      Box/Folder 14: 3
    - Outgoing, 1943 January 4-March 31
      Box/Folder 14: 4-6
    - Incoming, 1943 April 1 - 1944 April 30
      Box/Folder 14: 7-9
    - Outgoing, 1943 April 1 - 1944 April 30
      Box/Folder 14: 10-11
    - Outgoing, 1943 April 1 - 1944 April 30 (Reel 16)
      Box/Folder 14: 12
    - Chungking, 1943 June 1 - 1944 April 30
      Box/Folder 15: 1-3
    - Incoming, 1943 October 3 - 1944 September 1
      Box/Folder 15: 4-5
    - Outgoing, 1943 October 6 - 1944 August 24 (Reel 17)
      Box/Folder 15: 6-7
    - Miscellany, 1943-1944
      Box/Folder 15: 8
    - China Defense Supplies, 1944
      Box/Folder 15: 9
    - Incoming, 1944
      Box/Folder 16: 1
    - Outgoing, 1944
      Box/Folder 16: 2
    - Incoming, 1944 July 4 - 1945 April 6
      Box/Folder 16: 3-4
    - Incoming, 1944 July 4 - 1945 April 6 (Reel 18)
      Box/Folder 16: 5
    - Outgoing, 1944 July 14 - 1945 October 23
      Box/Folder 16: 6-7
    - Incoming, 1944 July 5 - 1945 July 30
      Box/Folder 16: 8
    - Outgoing, 1944 July 15 - 1945 July 31
      Box/Folder 16: 9
    - Chungking T. V. C. Office, 1944 May 4-August 31
      Box/Folder 17: 1
    - Chungking T. V. C. Office, 1944 May 4-August 31 (Reel 19)
      Box/Folder 17: 2-3
    - Incoming, 1944 July 17 - 1946 July 8
      Box/Folder 17: 4-6
    - Washington, D.C., 1945 October 23 - 1946 May 4 (Reel 20)
      Box/Folder 17: 7-9
    - Incoming, 1945 August 10 - 1946 April 12
      Box/Folder 18: 1
    - Outgoing, 1945 August 12 - 1946 April 12
      Box/Folder 18: 2
    - Miscellany, 1945 October 13 - 1946 March 27
      Box/Folder 18: 3-4
    - Incoming, 1945 October 1 - 1946 February 27 (Reel 21)
      Box/Folder 18: 5-6
    - Incoming, 1946 March 1-May 10
      Box/Folder 18: 7-8
    - Incoming, 1946 May 13-October 9
      Box/Folder 18: 9
    - Incoming, 1946 May 13-October 9 (Reel 22)
      Box/Folder 18: 10-11
    - Incoming-outgoing, 1946 April 27-September 6
      Box/Folder 19: 1-2
    - Outgoing, 1946 March 28-June 28
      Box/Folder 19: 3
    - Outgoing, 1946 May 6-September 6
      Box/Folder 19: 4
    - Incoming, 1946 July 12 - 1947 September 26 (Reel 23)
      Box/Folder 19: 5
    - Outgoing, 1946 September 7 - 1947 September 26
      Box/Folder 19: 6
    - Incoming-outgoing, 1947-1949
      Box/Folder 19: 7
    - Incoming-outgoing, 1948-1949
      Box/Folder 19: 8-9
- Subject File, 1935-1950
  Interviews, meeting notes, memoranda, printed materials, and reports, arranged alphabetically by title or subject.
  - Alsop, Joseph (Reel 24)
    Box/Folder 20: 1
  - Australia
    Box/Folder 20: 2
  - Banks and banking - China
    Box/Folder 20: 3
  - Beal, Jonathan R.
    Box/Folder 20: 4
  - Belgium, vols. I and II, 1941
    Box/Folder 20: 5
  - Biographical material
    - Biographies
      Box/Folder 20: 6
    - Daily schedule (incomplete), 1942 October - 1943 January
      Box/Folder 20: 7
    - Newspaper articles, interviews
      Box/Folder 20: 8. Typewritten copies.
  - Blandford, John
    Box/Folder 20: 9
  - Bond, W. L.
    Box/Folder 20: 10
  - Boxers - indemnities
    Box/Folder 20: 11
  - Buck, Pearl
    Box/Folder 20: 12
  - Bullitt, William C.
    Box/Folder 20: 13
  - Burma Road
    Box/Folder 20: 14
  - Burma-Yunnan Railway
    Box/Folder 20: 15
  - Byrnes, James F.
    Box/Folder 20: 16
  - California - Alien Land Laws
    Box/Folder 20: 17
  - Canada
    - Economic assistance - China - Mutual Aid Board Reports
      - 1
        Box/Folder 20: 18-20
      - 2 (Reel 25)
        Box/Folder 20: 21-23
      - 3
        Box/Folder 21: 1-2
      - 3 (Reel 26)
        Box/Folder 21: 3-6
    - Foreign relations - China
      Box/Folder 21: 7
    - Foreign relations - China (Reel 27)
      Box/Folder 21: 8-10
  - Canton - Customs Office
    Box/Folder 22: 1
  - Canton-Kowloon Highway
    Box/Folder 22: 2
  - Central Bank of China
    Box/Folder 22: 3-4
  - Chai, F. Y.
    Box/Folder 22: 5
  - Chang, H. H.
    Box/Folder 22: 6
  - Chen, Kwang Pu
    Box/Folder 22: 7
  - Chen, R. C.
    Box/Folder 22: 8
  - China
    - Agriculture
      Box/Folder 22: 9-10
    - Agriculture (Reel 28)
      Box/Folder 22: 11-12
    - Automobiles
      Box/Folder 23: 1
    - Central News Agency
      Box/Folder 23: 2
    - Commission on Aeronautical Affairs
      Box/Folder 23: 3
    - Communism
      Box/Folder 23: 4-5
    - Communism (Reel 29)
      Box/Folder 23: 6-9
    - Cotton industry
      Box/Folder 23: 10
    - Currency question
      - Allotment
        Box/Folder 23: 11
      - Stabilization
        Box/Folder 24: 1-2
      - Stabilization (Reel 30)
        Box/Folder 24: 3-5
    - Dike reconstruction
      Box/Folder 24: 6-7
    - Economic conditions
      - General (Reel 31)
        Box/Folder 25: 1-4
      - Gold sales
        Box/Folder 25: 5
    - Economic planning
      Box/Folder 25: 6
    - Embassy, Washington, D. C. (Reel 32)
      Box/Folder 25: 7
    - Firearms
      Box/Folder 25: 8
    - Foreign exchange
      Box/Folder 25: 9-10
    - Foreign relations
      - Great Britain
        Box/Folder 25: 11
      - Russia
        Box/Folder 26: 1
      - Tibet
        Box/Folder 26: 2
      - United States
        - General
          Box/Folder 26: 3
        - Economic assistance
          - 1940 (Reel 33)
            Box/Folder 26: 4
          - 1942-1943
            Box/Folder 26: 5
          - 1945-1946
            Box/Folder 26: 6
          - 1946-1947
            Box/Folder 26: 7-8
    - Imports
      Box/Folder 26: 9
    - Industrial development (Reel 34)
      Box/Folder 26: 10
    - Liquidity (economics)
      Box/Folder 26: 11
    - Medical care
      Box/Folder 26: 12
    - Ministry of Finance
      Box/Folder 27: 1-4
    - National land policy
      Box/Folder 27: 5
    - National Resources Commission
      Box/Folder 27: 6
    - Natural resources
      - Coal
        Box/Folder 27: 7
      - Metals (Reel 35)
        Box/Folder 27: 8
      - Oil
        Box/Folder 27: 9
      - Tungsten
        Box/Folder 27: 10
    - Northeast Four Provinces
      Box/Folder 27: 11
    - Pearl River
      Box/Folder 27: 12
    - Politics and government
      Box/Folder 27: 13
    - Railroads
      Box/Folder 27: 14
    - Rice
      Box/Folder 27: 15-17
    - Rice (cont'd.)
      Box/Folder 28: 1
    - Taxation
      Box/Folder 28: 2
    - Textile industry
      Box/Folder 28: 3
    - Shipping
      Box/Folder 28: 4
    - War Production Board
      Box/Folder 28: 5
    - Yangtze Power Company (Reel 36)
      Box/Folder 28: 6
  - China Defense Supplies, Inc.
    - Correspondence
      - 1941
        Box/Folder 28: 7
      - 1943
        Box/Folder 28: 8
      - 1944
        Box/Folder 28: 9-10
    - Memoranda
      Box/Folder 28: 11
    - Reports (Reel 37)
      Box/Folder 28: 12-15
    - Reports (cont'd.)
      Box/Folder 29: 1
  - China Development Finance Corporation (CDFC)
    Box/Folder 29: 2
  - China National Aviation Corporation (CNAC)
    Box/Folder 29: 3
  - Chinese Industrial Cooperatives (Indusco), International Committee
    Box/Folder 29: 4
  - Chinese National Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (CNRRA)
    Box/Folder 29: 5
  - Chinese Supply Commission (CSC)
    Box/Folder 29: 6
  - Chou En-lai
    Box/Folder 29: 7
  - Chungking - telephone service
    Box/Folder 29: 8
  - Churchill, Winston
    Box/Folder 29: 9
  - Davies, John Paton
    Box/Folder 29: 10
  - Dulles, John Foster
    Box/Folder 29: 11
  - Eden, Anthony
    Box/Folder 29: 12
  - Diplomats' wives list
    Box/Folder 29: 13
  - Fortune, 1945 April
    Box/Folder 29: 14
  - Frankfurter, Felix
    Box/Folder 29: 15
  - Gauss, Clarence
    Box/Folder 29: 16
  - Great Britain
    - Economic assistance - China
      Box/Folder 29: 17
    - Foreign relations - China
      Box/Folder 29: 18
  - Hainan Island
    Box/Folder 29: 19-20
  - Hainan Island (Reel 38)
    Box/Folder 29: 21
  - Henry, James
    Box/Folder 29: 22
  - Hong Kong
    Box/Folder 29: 23
  - Hopkins, Harry
    Box/Folder 29: 24
  - Hsiao, Sin-ju Pu
    Box/Folder 29: 25
  - Hsu, Shuhsi
    Box/Folder 30: 1-3
  - Hull, Cordell
    Box/Folder 30: 4
  - Hurley, Patrick
    Box/Folder 30: 5
  - Institute of Pacific Relations
    Box/Folder 30: 6
  - International conferences, U.S. Office of War Information (OWI) publication, Problems of War and Peace, 1941-1945
    Box/Folder 30: 7
  - International Labor Organization
    Box/Folder 30: 8
  - Jaspar, A. S. (Reel 39)
    Box/Folder 30: 9
  - Judd, Walter
    Box/Folder 30: 10
  - Keswick, John
    Box/Folder 30: 11
  - Kiang, H. C.
    Box/Folder 30: 12
  - Kiang, P., General
    Box/Folder 30: 13
  - Koo, Wellington
    Box/Folder 30: 14
  - Kowloon - Customs Office
    Box/Folder 30 :15
  - Kung, H. H.
    Box/Folder 30: 16
  - Kwangtung Province
    - Brewery
      Box/Folder 30: 17
    - Hydroelectric development
      Box/Folder 30: 18
    - Paper industry
      Box/Folder 30: 19
    - Ships and shipping
      Box/Folder 30: 20
    - Sugar
      Box/Folder 30: 21
    - Telephone development
      Box/Folder 30: 22
  - Leahy, William, Admiral
    Box/Folder 30: 23
  - Lend-lease operations, (1941-1945) (Reel 40)
    Box/Folder 31: 1-2
  - Lin, Yutang
    Box/Folder 31: 3
  - Liu, C. S.
    Box/Folder 31: 4
  - Maps
    Box/Folder 31: 5
  - Marshall, George C., General
    Box/Folder 31: 6
  - Medals, Chinese
    Box/Folder 31: 7
  - Ming Sung Industrial Company, Ltd.
    Box/Folder 31: 8
  - Miscellany
    Box/Folder 31: 9
  - Molin Ho
    Box/Folder 31: 10
  - Moscow Conference, 1943
    Box/Folder 31: 11
  - Pei, Tsu-yee
    Box/Folder 31: 12
  - Rajchman, Dr. Ludwig
    Box/Folder 31: 13
  - Reconstruction, (1939-1951)
    - Memoranda
      Box/Folder 31: 14
    - Reports
      - Post-War World Organization (Reel 41)
        Box/Folder 31: 15
      - Initial Reconstruction Program for China
        Box/Folder 31: 16-17
  - Red Cross
    Box/Folder 32: 1
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President
    Box/Folder 32: 2-3
  - Schuman, Frederick
    Box/Folder 32: 4
  - Shanghai - Customs Office
    Box/Folder 32: 5
  - Shaughnessy, Quinn
    Box/Folder 32: 6
  - Shen, Shi-Hwa
    Box/Folder 32: 7
  - Shigemitsu, Mamoru
    Box/Folder 32: 8
  - Singapore
    Box/Folder 32: 9
  - Sino-Japanese Conflict (1937-1945)
    Box/Folder 32: 10
  - Stimson, Henry
    Box/Folder 32: 11
  - Swatow
    - Customs Office
      Box/Folder 32: 12
    - Rationing
      Box/Folder 32: 13
  - Sze, Deson
    Box/Folder 32: 14
  - Sze, Ming-sze
    Box/Folder 32: 15
  - Tan, Shao-hwa (Reel 42)
    Box/Folder 32: 16
  - Thurston, Mr.
    Box/Folder 32: 17
  - Tong, Hollington K.
    Box/Folder 32: 18
  - Truman, Harry S., President
    Box/Folder 32: 19
  - United Nations
    - General
      Box/Folder 33: 1
    - Conference on International Organization
      Box/Folder 33: 2-4
    - Meeting of Five Ministers for Foreign Affairs, 1945 May 25 (Reel 43)
      Box/Folder 33: 5-6
  - United States
    - Department of State
      Box/Folder 33: 7
    - Economic assistance - China
      Box/Folder 33: 8
    - Economic Cooperation Administration (ECA) - China
      Box/Folder 33: 9
    - Export-Import Bank
      Box/Folder 33: 10
    - Foreign relations
      - China
        - General
          Box/Folder 33: 11
        - White Paper, 1949
          Box/Folder 33: 12
      - Great Britain
        Box/Folder 33: 13
  - Vincent, John Carter
    Box/Folder 33: 14
  - Wang, H.
    Box/Folder 33: 15
  - Wedemeyer, Albert C., General
    Box/Folder 34: 1
  - Whampoa - port development
    Box/Folder 34: 2
  - Willauer, Whiting
    Box/Folder 34: 3
  - Woo, Yat Kwong
    Box/Folder 34: 4
  - World War (1939-1945)
    - General
      Box/Folder 34: 5
    - China
      Box/Folder 34: 6
  - Yang, S. Z.
    Box/Folder 34: 7
  - Yin, K. Y.
    Box/Folder 34: 8
  - Young, Arthur N.
    Box/Folder 34: 9
  - Youngman, William S.
    Box/Folder 34: 10
- Speeches and Writings, 1941-1948
  Drafts, newspaper articles, notes, and speeches, arranged by title, subject, or place of speech.
  - Speech, American Legion Convention, 1942 August (Reel 44)
    Box/Folder 34: 11. Typescript, carbon copy (2 copies)
  - After-dinner speech, 1941 September 12
    Box/Folder 34: 12. Carbon copy.
  - Speech, China Society, undated
    Box/Folder 34: 13. Printed copy.
  - "China's Place in the Postwar World," speech outline, 1942 February 12
    Box/Folder 34: 14. Typescript.
  - Double Tenth Anniversary speech, 1947 October 10
    Box/Folder 34: 15. Typescript, carbon copies (3 copies).
  - Report, Kuomintang Standing Committee, undated
    Box/Folder 34: 16
  - Report, Kwangtung Provincial Assembly, 1948 June 24
    Box/Folder 34: 17. Typescript (2 copies).
  - Speech, Kwangtung Provincial Assembly, undated
    Box/Folder 34: 18. Typescript.
  - Meeting notes, May 29 (1 typescript, 2 carbon copies), June 28 (1 typescript, 1 carbon copy), June 29 (1 typescript, 2 carbon copies), and June 30 (1 typescript, 2 carbon copies), 1940
    Box/Folder 34: 19
  - New Year message, 1942 January 1
    Box/Folder 34: 20. Typescript.
  - Newspaper article, "Soong Replies to Control Yuan on Foreign Exchange,", 1947 October 7
    Box/Folder 34: 21. Printed copy, carbon copies (3 copies).
  - Proclamation - Kowloon City, undated
    Box/Folder 34: 22
  - "Proposed United Nations Charter," by T. V. Soong (?)
    Box/Folder 34: 23. Carbon copy.
  - Radio broadcast for British Broadcasting Company (BBC), London, 1943 August 8
    Box/Folder 34: 24. Carbon copy.
  - Speech, Rotary Club, 1948 March 10
    Box/Folder 34: 25. Carbon copy.
  - Speech, United Nations Conference on International Organization, 1945 April 30
    Box/Folder 34: 26. Printed copies.
  - Speech on World War II, 1942 March 6
    Box/Folder 34: 27. Drafts. Typescript, carbon copy (2 copies).
  - Speech, Washington Press Club, undated
    Box/Folder 34: 28. Typescript.
  - Speech, Yale University, 1942 June 9
    Box/Folder 34: 29. Typescript, printed copy (2 copies).
- Formerly Closed Material, circa 1934-1948
  Correspondence, lists, and other material, arranged alphabetically by correspondent, title, or subject.
  - Correspondence
    - Alsop, Joseph, 1943
      Box/Folder 34: 30
    - Chang, F., 1948
      Box/Folder 34: 31
    - Chen, R. C., 1941-1943
      Box/Folder 34: 32
    - Chennault, Claire L., General, 1943
      Box/Folder 34: 33
    - Chiang Kai-shek, 1940-1945
      Box/Folder 34: 34
    - Chow, C. J., General, 1943-1944
      Box/Folder 34: 35
    - Foo, P. S., 1943
      Box/Folder 34: 36
    - Gawler, G. N., 1948
      Box/Folder 34: 37
    - Grantham, Alexander, Sir, 1948
      Box/Folder 34: 38
    - Hollis, L. C., 1943
      Box/Folder 34: 39
    - Hopkins, Harry, 1942-1945
      Box/Folder 35: 1
    - Hsu, Tso Shan, 1942
      Box/Folder 35: 2
    - Kiang, H. C., 1941-1942
      Box/Folder 35: 3
    - Koo, Wellington, 1943-1947
      Box/Folder 35: 4
    - Koo, Y. C., 1943
      Box/Folder 35: 5
    - Kung, Ling-kai, 1946
      Box/Folder 35: 6
    - Leahy, William D., Admiral, 1943
      Box/Folder 35: 7
    - Li, Shu-fan, 1943
      Box/Folder 35: 8
    - Little, Lester K., 1947
      Box/Folder 35: 9
    - McCloy, John J., 1942
      Box/Folder 35: 10
    - McHugh, J. M., 1944
      Box/Folder 35: 11
    - McNarney, J. T., General, 1943
      Box/Folder 35: 12
    - McNeary, H. G., 1940
      Box/Folder 35: 13
    - Magruder, Carter, General, 1941-1942
      Box/Folder 35: 14
    - Pei, Tsu-yee, 1942-1944
      Box/Folder 35: 15
    - Price, Harry, 1944
      Box/Folder 35: 16
    - Rajchman, Ludwig, 1942-1943 (Reel 45)
      Box/Folder 35: 17
    - Rogers, Cyril, 1941-1946
      Box/Folder 35: 18
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1943
      Box/Folder 35: 19
    - Rorschach, A. L., 1947-1948
      Box/Folder 35: 20
    - Sun Yat-sen, 1946
      Box/Folder 35: 21
    - U.S. China Relief Mission, 1947
      Box/Folder 35: 22
    - Wedemeyer, Albert C., General, 1946
      Box/Folder 35: 23
    - Wu, K. C., 1943-1945
      Box/Folder 35: 24
    - Yen, Y. C. James, 1945
      Box/Folder 35: 25
    - Youngman, William S., 1944
      Box/Folder 35: 26
  - Office file
    - Telegrams (declassified) removed from
      - Box 11
        Box/Folder 35: 27
      - Box 12
        Box/Folder 35: 28
      - Box 13
        Box/Folder 35: 29
      - Box 14
        Box/Folder 35: 30
      - Box 15
        Box/Folder 35: 31
      - Box 16
        Box/Folder 35: 32
      - Box 17
        Box/Folder 35: 33
      - Box 18
        Box/Folder 35: 34
      - Box 19
        Box/Folder 35: 35
  - Subject file (declassified)
    - Alsop, Joseph
      Box/Folder 35: 36
    - Burma Road
      Box/Folder 35: 37
    - Central Bank of China, 1946-1947
      Box/Folder 35: 38
    - Chiang, Kai-shek
      Box/Folder 36: 1
    - Chiang, Kai-shek, Mme.
      Box/Folder 36: 2
    - China
      - Armed forces - Chennault, Claire L., "Politico-Military Situation in China,", 1944 October 26
        Box/Folder 36: 3
      - Communism
        Box/Folder 36: 4
      - Currency question - stabilization (Reel 46)
        Box/Folder 36: 5-6
      - Economic conditions
        - General
          Box/Folder 36: 7
        - Gold sales
          Box/Folder 36: 8
      - Economic planning
        Box/Folder 36: 9
      - Foreign exchange
        Box/Folder 36: 10
      - Foreign relations
        - Netherlands
          Box/Folder 36: 11
        - Russia
          Box/Folder 36: 12
        - U.S.
          - General
            Box/Folder 36: 13
          - Economic assistance
            Box/Folder 36: 14
      - Imports
        Box/Folder 36: 15
      - Industrial development
        Box/Folder 36: 16
      - Natural resources - metal
        Box/Folder 36: 17
    - Chinese-British-American Conference, Calcutta, Indian, 1943 February
      Box/Folder 36: 18
    - Chinese National Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (CNRRA)
      Box/Folder 36: 19
    - Chinese students in the U.S. - Technician Training Program (proposed)
      Box/Folder 36: 20
    - Davis, John
      Box/Folder 36: 21
    - Gauss, Clarence
      Box/Folder 36: 22
    - Hong Kong
      Box/Folder 36: 23
    - Hopkins, Harry
      Box/Folder 37: 1
    - Hurley, Patrick
      Box/Folder 37: 2
    - Knox, Frank
      Box/Folder 37: 3
    - Kowloon - Customs Office
      Box/Folder 37: 4
    - Kung, H. H.
      Box/Folder 37: 5
    - Leahy, William, Admiral
      Box/Folder 37: 6
    - Lend-lease operations (1941-1945) (Reel 47)
      Box/Folder 37: 7
    - Macao
      Box/Folder 37: 8
    - McCloy, John J.
      Box/Folder 37: 9
    - Marshall, George C., General
      Box/Folder 37: 10
    - Moscow Conference, 1943
      Box/Folder 37: 11
    - Pei, Tsu-yee
      Box/Folder 37: 12
    - Public opinion - U.S.
      Box/Folder 37: 13
    - Quebec Conference, 1944
      Box/Folder 37: 14
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President
      Box/Folder 37: 15
    - Shanghai - Customs Office
      Box/Folder 37: 16
    - Soong, T. V. - lists of files
      Box/Folder 37: 17
    - Stilwell, Joseph, General
      Box/Folder 37: 18
    - Tacheng (Sinkiang) - Customs Office
      Box/Folder 37: 19
    - Timberman, Thomas, Colonel
      Box/Folder 37: 20
    - United States
      - Congress
        Box/Folder 37: 21
      - Economic Cooperation Administration (ECA), China
        Box/Folder 37: 22
      - Embassy, Chungking
        Box/Folder 37: 23
      - Foreign relations - China - general
        Box/Folder 37: 24
    - Wedemeyer, Albert C., General
      Box/Folder 37: 25
    - Wells, Sumner
      Box/Folder 37: 26
    - Wood, W. H.
      Box/Folder 37: 27
    - World War (1939-1945)
      - General
        Box/Folder 37: 28
      - Chiefs of Staff Committee, India Command
        Box/Folder 37: 29
      - China
        Box/Folder 37: 30
      - Pacific War Council
        Box/Folder 37: 31
      - Reparations
        Box/Folder 37: 32
    - Young, Arthur (Reel 48)
      Box/Folder 38: 1-2
- Correspondence [Chinese language], 1942-1947
  - Ah-ying, 1945
    Box/Folder 38: 3
  - Bank of Chinese Products, 1945
    Box/Folder 38: 4
  - Chang, Fu-ch'eng, 1947?
    Box/Folder 38: 5
  - Chang, Han-ch'ing, 1947?
    Box/Folder 38: 6
  - Chang, Shao-chuang (Hsü), 1943
    Box/Folder 38: 7
  - Chang, T'ing-o, 1945
    Box/Folder 38: 8
  - Chang, Tzu-k'ai, 1945
    Box/Folder 38: 9
  - Chang, Yu-hua (Cheng), 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 10
  - Ch'en, Chih-p'ing, 1947
    Box/Folder 38: 11
  - Ch'en, Hsiao-wei, 1946?
    Box/Folder 38: 12
  - Ch'en, Po-kung, 1945
    Box/Folder 38: 13
  - Ch'en, Yü-ch'ien, 1945
    Box/Folder 38: 14
  - Ch'en, Yüan-chu, 1945
    Box/Folder 38: 15
  - Cheng, Chih-hsiang, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 16
  - Chi-nan ta hsüeh, Hsiang-kang t'ung hsüeh hui, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 17
  - Chiang, Hsiao-lu, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 18
  - Chiang, Hsin-te, 1946?
    Box/Folder 38: 19
  - Chiang, Meng-lin, 1945?
    Box/Folder 38: 20
  - Ch'ien, Ch'ang-chao, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 21
  - Ch'ien, Hsin-chih, 1946?
    Box/Folder 38: 22
  - China. Wai-chiao pu, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 23
  - Ching, Yu-yen, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 24
  - Ch'ing yüan hsien li Ching yüan chung hsüeh, 1947
    Box/Folder 38: 25
  - Chou, I-ch'un, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 26
  - Chu, Chiao-feng, 1945
    Box/Folder 38: 27
  - Chu, Hsiu-feng, 1947
    Box/Folder 38: 28
  - Chu, Hui-chün (Chao), 1942?
    Box/Folder 38: 29
  - Chung-hua nung yeh hui, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 30
  - Chung hua sheng kung hui, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 31
  - Chung kuo kungchan tang, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 32
  - Comite Hoakiauw Penoendjang Gerakan Amal di Tiongkok
    Box/Folder 38: 33
  - Cornell University, Chinese Students Union, 1943
    Box/Folder 38: 34
  - Feng, Yü-hsiang, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 35
  - Cheng, I., undated
    Box/Folder 38: 36
  - Ho, Hao-jo, 1946?
    Box/Folder 38: 37
  - Hsiang-kang Hua shang tsung hui, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 38
  - Hsieh, Kuan-sheng, undated
    Box/Folder 38: 39
  - Hsü, Po-yüan, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 40
  - Hsü, Yün-chih, 1947
    Box/Folder 38: 41
  - Hu, Mu-lan, 1946?
    Box/Folder 38: 42
  - Hu, Yü-sun, 1945?
    Box/Folder 38: 43
  - Huang, Ch'iang, 1942
    Box/Folder 38: 44
  - Huang, Po-chiao, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 45
  - Hung, Kuei, 1947?
    Box/Folder 38: 46
  - Kan-shu t'ung hsiang hui, 1946
    Box/Folder 38: 47
  - Kuang-hua jih pao, 1945
    Box/Folder 38: 48